ANTONY BUDIANTO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER AND OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTOR



PROFILE

Name: Antony Budianto DOB: August 8th, 1993 From: Pontianak, Indonesia

EDUCATION

Binus UniversityBachelor degree of Information
Systems major
2015

SKILLS

Technical skills

- HTML, CSS, JS, TypeScript
- React platform (Web, Native, VR)
- Angular JS, Angular
- Jest, Webpack
- NodeJS, Java, Golang
- Git, Jenkins + Travis CI, Docker

Soft skills

- Team-player, fast learner
- · Languages: English, Indonesia

SUMMARY

A software engineer and open source contributor with 4+ years experience on software development, web design and development, git, writing unit and end-to-end tests, deployment and setup CI server. Actively contributing to open source and listed as one of the top 10 JavaScript GitHub developer in Indonesia by git-awards.com

EXPERIENCE

Tokopedia | Frontend Engineer

Sep 2017 - present

Developed Fintech web apps using React and unit test using Jest

GDP Labs | Sr. Software Development Engineer

Sep 2016 - Aug 2017

• Developed HR platform web apps using Angular 2

GDP Labs | Software Development Engineer

Sep 2015 - Aug 2016

Developed vehicle insurance enterprise application using Angular JS

Binus University | Network Administrator

Sep 2014 - Aug 2015

 Cloning images for software lab computers, ensure networks running well, patching, calibration, maintenance, and develop various network-based applications

Binus University | Teaching Assistant

Sep 2013 - Aug 2014

• Teach various programming languages in software lab classes

PROJECT

CRA Universal

https://github.com/antonybudianto/cra-universal

- CLI to initialize universal create-react-app without ejecting
- Supports server-side rendering with code splitting

Gitfun

https://gitfun-web.herokuapp.com

- Simple GitHub client browser and repository summary
- Available on Web and Android (React Native)

Generated using https://github.com/antonybudianto/react-resume